Rahaf Salti

PESRONAL DETAILS

Nationality
Birthday
Email
Address
Phones

LinkedIn

Palestinian 26/9/1992

rahafsalti@gmail.com

Syria, Damascus, Al-Mazzah

MOBILE: +963-991-741-787 HOME: +963-11-611-53-54

https://www.linkedin.com/in/salti-rahaf-716a456b

SUMMARY

A hard worker, effective team planner, and a good consultant, and looking forward to my next opportunity in a job that I can improve my experience with and effectively utilize my strong points.

Currently working at SoftCad for ICT solutions as an application developer developing a new ERP for the Ministry of Education based on Oracle database and ASP.net and worked on maintaining the old ERP reports which were developed using Oracle Report.

Have gained an experience during my fourth year of studying by joining a training program at AMeSCOM as database developer, and contributed to the company research for designing distributed object-oriented database interface based on MySQL.

EXPERIENCE

1 March 2016 – Present

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - SoftCad

- + Analysis, redesign and develop ERP (Oracle Database, ASP.net)
- + Solve and maintain client problems in the old ERP (Oracle Report, Oracle Database)
- + Prepare and setup Windows application and Oracle database servers, and take database backups
- + Train the end users on the system

21 Sept 2014

CONTESTANT IN SYRIAN COLLEGIATE PROGRAMMING CONTEST

28 Aug 2014

CONTESTANT IN SYRIAN PRIVATE UNIVERSITIES PROGRAMMING CONTEST

Sept 2013 – March 2014

DATABASE DEVELOPER – AMeSCOM (training)

- + Develop MySQL database triggers
- + Work on solving replication problem between sites.
- + Build Facebook application and it's interface to link between ERP users and their Facebook notification icon over SSL.

EDUCATION

Sep 2010 – Feb 2016

BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING – Yarmouk Private University

AGPA is 3.36 out of 4

- Knowledge-based System, Modeling and Simulation, Genetic Algorithms, Natural Language Processing, Image Processing
- + Artificial Intelligence (Prolog)
- + Internet Technologies & Web Programming (PHP + JavaScript +CSS + HTML)
- + Database (SQL Server + PL/SQL+ Oracle), Data Mining.
- + System Programming (C)
- + Introduction to Computer Graphics (OpenGL)
- + Operating System (Linux + Bash)
- + Programming, and Algorithm Analysis and Design (C++, C#, Java)
- + Computer Network and Security

PROJECTS

Oct 2015 – Feb 2016

REAL-TIME INFORMATION RETRIEVAL SYSTEM USING FACE RECOGNITION

The system gathers the users' information from Facebook App, then the facial features are extracted using EmguCv and indexed. An Android app contains a camera view that detects the face and send it to server which retrieves the information to the app.

Feb 2015 - Jun 2015

SMART WARDROBE

This android application suggests for you the best outfit to wear from your clothes according to the current weather. The application obtains the weather from Yahoo Weather provider, the logic is implemented with the JFuzzyLogic library, and using SQLite for database.

Sep 2014 - Feb 2015

3D MODELING VIRTUAL COACH

The project studies the 3D modeling of interactive technology in sport. The visualization has been developed in using Unity3D game engine to provide real time interactivity. A set of visualization parameters have been identified by the Microsoft Kinect version 2 and adjusted by graphical user interface to provide artistic control of the visualization.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

- + Native language is Arabic (Mother Tongue).
- + English is Excellent (All my studying of software engineering was in English language)
- + French is intermediate (gained from being in France for 2 years)
- + Spanish is elementary

SOFTWARE

Linux, Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop, SQL Server, SQL Oracle Developer, Eclipse, MatLab, Unity

SOCIAL

Good communication skills.

Flexible & adaptable, able to work well individually and within a team.